We were worried
about you.
Don't be melodramatic.
I'm just getting on a train
and leaving forever.
So a few things
don't go your way
and your best
decision
is to ride the
rails like a hobo?
Leonard, I am overwhelmed.
(Sheldon:)Everything
is changing,
and it's simply too much.
I need to get away and think.
(Scene:)Sheldon...
Yes?
I'm gonna miss you.
Of course you are.
You just made
that easier.
(Sheldon:)Excuse me.
(Sheldon:)Is it at all possible
(Sheldon:)that you're knitting
a pair of pants?
(Sheldon:)Oh, well, no, you're
understandably terrified.
(Sheldon:)But, you know,
allow me to explain.
(Sheldon:)45 days ago, um,
I embarked on
(Sheldon:)a railroad journey
of healing